# FRONTEND DEVELOPER

(REACT, REDUX, TYPESCRIPT)

## DARIA SHNIPOVA



t.me/dasha\_shsh



+37529-513-92-66



dshnipova@gmail.com



linkedin.com



github.com codewars.com



### **Summary**

Result oriented and enthusiastic Frontend developer experienced in creating SPA with the usage of React, Redux, TypeScript CSS3, HTML5. Every day I strive to learn new technology and work on improving my skills in React and JavaScript. In the future I see myself as a Full Stack Developer.

#### **Skills**



## Language

English • Intermediate/B2 (in progress)

#### **Interests**

Codewars, StackOverflow, Habr, Dev.to, English, reading.

## **Work experience** React Developer

Freelance

Portfolio: github.io/portfolio\_shnipovadev

09/2020-present

- · code migrating to TypeScript
- · reusable components development
- · registration and login form creation
- bug fixing, code refactoring
- · unit testing

#### **QA** Trainee

(EXP)CAPITAL · Minsk, Belarus

03/2020 - 05/2020

- · experience in Fintech project
- · smoke, functional, GUI testing of web/mobile apps
- bug reporting in Asana

#### **Senior Customs officer**

VITEBSK CUSTOMS · Vitebsk, Belarus

2013-2020

- · working with goods data bases of customs authorities
- · registration and checking of customs declarations

#### **Education**

IT-incubator

Minsk

React, Redux, TypeScript, JavaScript, HTML5/CSS3 2020

Software testing courses

Minsk 2019

Vitebsk State Technological University Bachelor's degree · Manager-economist 2009-2013